{
    "subject": "Yves_Angelo",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Colonel_Chabert__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Yves Angelo directed the film Colonel Chabert (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9024533629417419,
            "question": "Who directed the film Colonel Chabert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8844192624092102,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Yves Angelo."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.869908332824707,
            "question": "Is Yves Angelo known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8564225435256958,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Yves Angelo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7339602112770081,
            "question": "What year was the film Colonel Chabert released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6775438189506531,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Yves Angelo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6382301449775696,
            "question": "Who might have acted in Colonel Chabert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6372855305671692,
            "question": "What is the story about Colonel Chabert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312270760536194,
            "question": "In what year was Colonel Chabert released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5484709143638611,
            "question": "What genre is the film Colonel Chabert likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yves Angelo directed the film Colonel Chabert (1994).",
            "html": "yago_14899_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was Colonel Chabert released?",
            "html": "yago_14899_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the story about Colonel Chabert?",
            "html": "yago_14899_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have acted in Colonel Chabert?",
            "html": "yago_14899_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14899_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents indicate that Yves Angelo directed \"Colonel Chabert\" in 1994, which matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}